All pirates searching for the treasure One Piece must brave the second half of the Grand Line.
These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World.
Gold Roger and his crew were the only men to ever chart these waters and learn all the secrets they held.
For the rest of the pirates of the world, this has proven to be the end of the world, a graveyard of dreams.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber after eating the gum gum fruit, sets sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I will be the king of the pirates!
During their journey to the New World, Luffy and his crew arrive on Fishman Island, which is located 10,000 meters below sea level.
The Fishman Pirates, led by Horty Jones and assisted by Vander Decken, plot to overthrow King Neptune.
It is not long before the Straw Hats get pulled into the conflict and find themselves in the midst of an all-out war.
After a change of plans, Horty threatens to crush the entire island under the weight of a massive ship.
Either way, the whole island is doomed!
That includes your friends, the princess, and everyone else down there!
You're just a weakling, get it? You can't protect anyone!
Watch me! I'll save them all!
I've trained for two years! I'm ready!
A massive, confused fight! The Straw Hats versus the new Fishman Pirates!
You think you can save them all? Oh, that's rich. You talk a big game, don't you, Straw Hat?
This is crazy! He turned his back on Decken, too?
Sister! Swim away! It's up to you to save our people, Shirahoshi!
It's a bit late for that.
A bit late? What is that supposed to mean?
Donut! Isn't Decken on the brink of death right now?
If he dies or passes out, then no one goes back to normal, right?
He's power will go away, and the ship will stop following her!
And that means... that...
It'll hit the island!
Why'd you kick me? That hurt!
Suck it up! I'll kick you as many times as it takes!
You're such a meaty!
Even the captain would have kicked me for no reason!
Well, you shouldn't have hurt Nami.
You big waste of space.
How about another goose egg to match?
No! Get away!
Next time, be careful!
Where you drop your fat ass!
Nami!
Please don't get any scratches on that hot body!
Not another one!
Give me a break!
Watch out! She's dangerous!
Last time she used that magic wand thing, she did some major damage!
Ha! Black Ball!
What's she doing there?
She must be some kind of witch!
A witch? That's rude, you guys!
Hm.
How about Enchantress? That's much nicer!
But it's not magic! More like advanced meteorology, you might say!
Ah! Uh-oh!
Uh-oh!
Squirt Cloud Rod, go!
Ah!
What the?
Help me, I'm dying!
Stay back!
I can't let you touch me, hee!
Or I'll be dried squid!
Go ahead!
Icarus!
Did you notice how distraught the black-suited buffoon was when that woman fell to the ground?
I believe...
We may have discovered his weakness.
Oh yeah!
I'll make sure she can't move.
You can do the gruesome part!
Leave it to me, hee!
See, if you don't want to get yourself zapped, you shouldn't be playing with lightning.
Ah!
Hey!
Did something just grab me?
Huh?
Murhi!
You can be dried squid instead!
Wait, what's going on?
I can't move!
Somebody help me!
Anybody!
Nami?
Oh, that's right!
Here you go!
Say hello to the squid spear!
While you're standing there, could I see your pet-
So you're on their side.
Well, I'm glad I stabbed you then.
I'll drain you dry, hee!
Huh?
What's the matter?
When my spear stabs you, you're supposed to bleed out and turn into dry squid!
What am I doing wrong?
Come on!
Why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why?
Tell me, hee!
Well...
Being a skeleton, I'm already dry as a bone.
You're what?!
Ugh!
But how can that be, hee!
It is a rather complicated concept.
But, if you must know, when people died, their skin rots and-
That's not what I was talking about!
Oh, I see.
Well, about 50 years ago...
Geez!
What's the point of having a badass robot if everybody's too chicken to fight it?
Huh?
Oh, are you okay, boss?
Who are you?
Frankie!
Come on, you don't know a super guy like me?
Ah, you're one of their officers, ain't ya?
You should have the backbone to fight me at least!
I'm a squid, but I've got backbone!
Backbone?
We have that in common!
My brother!
You're such a bonehead!
Hey, skeleton!
I'd move away from there if I were you!
Huh?
Why's that?
Just... move!
Why did I step in?
Um... his face!
Whoa, what's he doing there?
He must have been the reason I couldn't move my legs!
Oh, hello.
And who might you be?
How did you like that?
Huh?
You've just suffered a devastating headbutt to your foot!
Uh...
Prepare to enter a world of pain!
Yes, any moment now!
He can't admit he's getting stepped on!
I'm sorry I stepped on you!
He said it!
Uh-oh!
It's a special technique I developed for delivering a headbutt where you least expect it!
I call it...
The Super Soul Headbutt!
Don't give it a name!
Come out, come out, wherever you are!
It's time for some payback!
Cha-cha!
You're no match for me underground!
Now I'm gonna chew you up and spit you out!
Star rumor!
If you're not careful, there won't be any ground left for us to stand on!
You don't have to dig that many tunnels, do you?
All right!
Hey, Chopper!
You all done?
Need some help out here!
Heh!
I bet I can catch this guy off guard!
Oh boy!
Almost too easy!
Hey!
Chopper!
Jeez, can he hear me?
I'll crush you into the ground, Simpson!
Oh, so, look out!
Oh!
Nice going!
So are all the tunnels connected?
Yeah, we're good to go!
Good to go.
Sweet.
Now, special attack, Green Star.
Wait for it, Skull Bomb Grass.
Too bad for you, Shorty.
We already fought a tunnel digger back in Alabasta,
so we're pros now.
Practice makes perfect, am I right?
Uh-huh.
Yeah, yeah!
You trying to make fools out of us?
You screwed up my hard work!
I'm gonna pulverize you like the little bug you are!
I can do some pulverizing myself!
I'll bite that ugly nose off!
Yeah, it's too bad you can't reach it.
Pack me up here, Chopper.
Are you still there?
Uh-oh.
Heya, buddy!
Looks like it's my turn now!
Cuckoo!
He-he-he!
Come down!
Ready, hee!
Stupid head, now you've made me angry!
I'm gonna beat you up good!
You might even cry!
That's it! I like your style, kid!
Finally I get to really let loose!
Oh no! Let me treat your injuries!
It's okay dear, don't cry!
Daddy!
Over here! He needs help!
Damn it, Horty! These people weren't even armed! How the hell could you do this to them?
Her Majesty, is she safe now?
I've got no idea. I wish I did. But wherever she is, I'm sure she's fighting for us.
Madam Charlie, what's gonna happen to Fish Man Island? Are we gonna die?
What about the guy with the straw hat? Is he gonna come back here and save us?
I'm scared, Madam Charlie! Say something!
We should pray.
Huh?
All we can do is pray Princess Shirohoshi and the others are safe.
We're helpless.
If we lose them, then we've lost all hope of survival.
So....
Heh. So desperate.
Stay away from the island, Noah! Please!
Shirahose!
If the Noah falls now, it's all over!
It's all over!
No! She came here!
Stop swimming upward!
Sister! You have to change your course before it's too late!
They figured it out!
Shirohoshi!
Touchplacer!
Brother Nye!
Ryuboshi!
The plan is set. Do not interfere.
Hey! Hey! Hold on!
If Decken dies, his ability will stop working.
You see, I stabbed him so that the Noah would fall.
So that's it!
If she keeps swimming straight up,
the ship's just gonna crash right into the island!
No matter how far away she swims,
the problem's just gonna get worse!
After her!
We gotta go tell her what to do!
Right!
Shirohoshi!
Winky Hoshi!
Stop right there.
I won't let you ruin this.
It's far too convenient for me.
Without even raising a finger,
I can crush my enemies in one shot,
including your meddlesome crew.
Stay with me!
Shirohoshi!
You've gotta swim through the side!
Sister!
She... she heard you!
Yes.
Useless mermaid!
This isn't over!
She's pulling away from the island!
And just in time, too!
You're getting on my nerves.
I'll make you pay for that!
I don't think so!
You brat!
You're not gonna hurt!
Weepy Hoshi!
Watch me!
Noah!
Please follow me!
I can't hold him!
Just a little farther!
This way!
Let's go!
Anderdecken!
Would you just hurry up and die already?
Hordy...
I'll get my revenge!
Whatever it takes!
If I stop, they will all be killed!
The ship!
It's starting to move to the side!
Yeah, you're doing great!
Almost there!
Keep swimming!
Hurry!
My left hand touched you!
So...
You're going to be my final target!
I'll run you into the ground!
I will chase you to the gates of hell!
Noah!
You mustn't give up now, Shirohoshi!
If it misses the island, then this was all for nothing!
Even if I die, you can't escape me!
Stay back!
Honey!
You're almost there!
Don't stop!
Taken!
It's over!
You've lost!
If you won't move, I'll move you!
Yeah, bring it on!
My axe will end this once and for all!
Shut Slater!
I'll protect everyone!
It's over!
Take it!
You've lost!
It's over!
If you won't move, I'll move you!
Yeah, bring it on!
My axe will end this once and for all!
Shut Slater!
I'll protect everyone!
We were too late!
It's falling!
It's right on target, too.
They're all going to die!
Is there nothing we can do?
It can't be!
Now this island will bring in a new era!
Yeah!
Luffy tries to lure Horty to the deck of the Noah,
but his plan is thwarted when the fishman destroys the bubble maintaining oxygen on the ship.
Fukuboshi faces off with Horty himself, but cannot match the strength of his foe.
As Horty reaches a new level of strength, Luffy must place his faith in a life-or-death gamble.
On the next One Piece, Luffy loses the fight, Horty's long-awaited revenge!
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!
In a chair, Oklahoma!
In a chair was definitely qua spaceend, T- één,
In a chair, man!
In the chair was able to do a few feet while raising that milestone behind by Horty's.
Hi-Roy!
Now you shall kind of go away from my hands within our hearts and knees ile.